

Summary

Oversee a team of 4 members. Experience in Quality Assurance in **Finance domain** specializing with Banking Applications and implementation of QA methodologies. Experience in Manual and Automation Testing includes System, Functional, Interface, Regression, User Acceptance. Experience in Quality Assurance in web based Applications and implementation of QA methodologies.

Employment

C-EDGE Technology (TCS-SBI Enterprise)

Navi Mumbai Nov. 2021 to Current

System Analyst

Experience in team management and ability to provide direction to encourage the achievement of project or company objectives.

Having good business knowledge and understanding functional flow of Payment gateway (SBIePay - Aggregator module), E- Commerce.

Bit Hub Technology

Software Test Engineer

Pune Aug. 2018 to Nov. 2021

Involved in QA Life Cycle, which includes Design, Developing and execution of the entire QA Process and documentation of Test Plans, Test Strategy, Test Cases and Test Scripts to ensure proper business compliance

Projects

Bank Integration

Knowledge of various Bank Transaction flow e.g. UCO Bank (Retail and Corporate), Janta Sahakari Bank (Retail), Axis Bank (Retail and Corporate) etc. with recon refund process.

Roles & Responsibilities:

- Documented Test plan and test cases , Wrote Test Cases and Test Scripts for the functional testing.
- Defect raised and Defect retest
- Checking Logs, DB.
- Recon and Refund.
- · Performing Regression testing.

Merchant Integration

- Automation testing done for Merchant Onboarding with GUI testing where each screen is checked to validate each functionality by executing test.
- REST full web services Automation in Java and testing
- Testing Transaction flow.

e.Agri Basket : E-Commerce application

Aug. 2018 to Sept. 2019

Roles & Responsibilities:

- $\bullet \ {\sf Reviewed \ Business \ Requirement \ Documents \ and \ Technical \ Specification}.$
- Design test cases/ test data.
- Participated in regular requirement and status call with client.
- $\bullet \ \, \text{Involved in Integration Testing, System Testing, Compatibility testing, Usability Testing} \\$
- Assisting the performance team for test execution. Supporting for UAT.

Smart Store : CRM application

Oct. 2019 to Oct. 2021

Roles & Responsibilities:

- Documented Test plan and test cases , Wrote Test Cases and Test Scripts for the functional testing.
- Performing Functionality, System, and Full Regression testing.
- Preparing the strategy document that defines the test environment, phases of testing, resources required to conduct the effort and training on the

functionality.

- Ensure that as many defects as possible, in both software and documentation are removed from a product before it reaches the customer.
- Daily metrics like number of defects per module was reported to the project Manager.
- Minimized redundancy in test cases by applying equivalence class testing techniques.

Contact

gorearti14@gmail.com
9664514284 / 9619510864

Education

A.C. Patil College of Engg. July 2011 to June 2014

M.E. Computer

D.Y.Patil College of Engg.

Aug. 2001 to June

B.E. Computer

Skills

Automation Testing Postman Thunder Client SQL Testing Selenium Webdriver Java TestNG

JIRA